What are you doing?
I can't let this a**hole
see this
Hong Il-tak
is looking hot today
- Move, you b******!
- You son of a…
So what?
Want to drink
with us later?
Yeah, okay
Only the guys
who paid get to come
but I'll make
an exception for you
Thanks
I'll go ahead
Come to Room 311 in a bit
Hey, Lee Hyeon-wu
You didn't pay
so don't f***ing come
I wasn't going to
you a**hole
Go on, why are you
looking at me?
Okay
Just don't drink
too much
There I go again
worrying about him
He'll be fine on his own
From Hee-seong's gang
in Class 3
to Yeong-jo's crew
in Class 7
All the second-year
bullies are here
Have a drink, Il-tak
Chug it down
- Cheers!
- Nice, nice
That's all
you're drinking?
Jeong-tae
is a total lightweight
I wonder
what Hyeon-wu is doing
Hey
You guys get out
for a minute
Are you deaf?
Everyone get out
except for Hong Il-tak